Réponse:
The lead organization is "Planète Urgence," and its website is www.planete-urgence.org.

Metadata: {'uid': 'ae52d35677004ad29990a4a7053b17f8', 'question': 'Q1.1 Lead organisation’s full name and website ??', 'enhanced_question': 'What is the full name and website of the lead organization?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': 'The lead organization is "Planète Urgence," and its website is www.planete-urgence.org.'}

Réponse:
The registered address of the lead organization, Planète Urgence, is 15 rue de la Fontaine au Roi, 75011 Paris.

Metadata: {'uid': '92ded4897f924ae5b5599f699a529d56', 'question': 'Q1.2 Lead organisation’s registered address ??', 'enhanced_question': 'What is the registered address of the lead organization?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': 'The registered address of the lead organization, Planète Urgence, is 15 rue de la Fontaine au Roi, 75011 Paris.'}

Réponse:
I don't know.

Metadata: {'uid': '0f36cc721809420c9fd37fd2a421514d', 'question': "Indicate details relating to each of the financial annual report and accounts that you are required to upload in the Section Terms and conditions, and attachments. In the table below, first enter the dates and currency of your organisation's financial report and accounts. Then, enter the annual income of the lead organisation in the original currency of the accounts. Finally, convert the original currency and enter the annual income in British Pound Sterling (GBP). ??", 'enhanced_question': 'What is the original text you would like translated, or do you have another text for translation?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': "I don't know."}

Réponse:
Planète Urgence is an NGO (non-governmental organization) of international solidarity and development that was created in 2000 and is recognized as being of public utility.

Metadata: {'uid': 'c166bd9321e341109e55c0f943d1cf19', 'question': 'Q1.4 Lead organisation’s legal status ??', 'enhanced_question': 'What is the legal status of the lead organization?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': 'Planète Urgence is an NGO (non-governmental organization) of international solidarity and development that was created in 2000 and is recognized as being of public utility.'}

Réponse:
The primary focus of the lead organization, Planète Urgence, is to strengthen individuals and communities to preserve forests and biodiversity. They aim to promote local development in communities that coexist with forests, raise awareness about environmental issues, and engage local educational actors to sensitize and involve children in protecting their environment, particularly concerning climate, biodiversity, and forests.

Metadata: {'uid': 'ebbc0ef6b8554cf1bdc7f4b167333e43', 'question': 'Q1.5 Lead organisation’s primary focus ??', 'enhanced_question': 'What is the primary focus of the lead organization?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': 'The primary focus of the lead organization, Planète Urgence, is to strengthen individuals and communities to preserve forests and biodiversity. They aim to promote local development in communities that coexist with forests, raise awareness about environmental issues, and engage local educational actors to sensitize and involve children in protecting their environment, particularly concerning climate, biodiversity, and forests.'}

Réponse:
The lead organization involved in the project is Planète Urgence, which operates with a strong territorial approach, collaborating with local partners to provide field expertise in alignment with national and local public policies. They focus on addressing identified and formalized needs within the communities they serve. Their experience includes coordinating projects with local authorities to ensure sustainable management of territories, supporting local organizations and communities in environmental projects, promoting reforestation, developing sustainable economic sectors linked to natural resources, and raising awareness about forest protection. Additionally, Planète Urgence has sent 11,111 volunteers on missions, demonstrating their commitment to engagement and action in various regions.

Metadata: {'uid': '72e32f47881147be9d246e108da59618', 'question': 'Q1.6 Lead organisation’s experience and expertise ??', 'enhanced_question': 'What is the experience and expertise of the lead organization involved in the project?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': 'The lead organization involved in the project is Planète Urgence, which operates with a strong territorial approach, collaborating with local partners to provide field expertise in alignment with national and local public policies. They focus on addressing identified and formalized needs within the communities they serve. Their experience includes coordinating projects with local authorities to ensure sustainable management of territories, supporting local organizations and communities in environmental projects, promoting reforestation, developing sustainable economic sectors linked to natural resources, and raising awareness about forest protection. Additionally, Planète Urgence has sent 11,111 volunteers on missions, demonstrating their commitment to engagement and action in various regions.'}

Réponse:
I don't know.

Metadata: {'uid': '1e403fb5351041f296c258d01f29fa65', 'question': 'What year was your organisation formally established and legally registered?', 'enhanced_question': 'Which language would you like the text to be translated into?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': "I don't know."}

Réponse:
I don't know.

Metadata: {'uid': '7c3b1cab599b4b7facd624c1d7f15c5d', 'question': 'How is your organisation currently funded?', 'enhanced_question': 'What language do you need the text translated into?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'asso', 'source_doc_language': 'french', 'translation_requiered': True, 'response': "I don't know."}

Réponse:
I don't know.

Metadata: {'uid': '0027b103e48b4ede97dc5b39ab91ac4c', 'question': 'Has your organisation ever applied for Overseas Development Assistance (ODA) funding? NOTE: ODA is defined as government aid designed to promote the economic development and welfare of\ndeveloping countries.', 'enhanced_question': 'Has your organization previously applied for Overseas Development Assistance (ODA) funding, which is government aid aimed at promoting economic development and welfare in developing countries?', 'question_close_or_open': 'close', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'pp', 'source_doc_language': 'english', 'translation_requiered': False, 'response': "I don't know."}

Graphrag pipeline in progress

Metadata: {'uid': '8d129cdaa2ab483b86187af5515155b5', 'question': 'What are the aims of your organisation?', 'enhanced_question': 'What are the objectives of your organization?', 'question_close_or_open': 'open', 'question_asso_or_pp': 'pp', 'source_doc_language': 'english', 'translation_requiered': False, 'response': "I don't know."}

Impossible de détetminer le type de question asso/pp